(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
僕たちは配信アプリ、ホロキャスで活動する配信者。
We are streamers active on the streaming app, HoloCas.
突然画面に吸い込まれて、
Suddenly sucked into the screen,
アプリと繋がる謎の世界、ホロキャス界に来ちゃった！
we arrived in the mysterious HoloCas World connected to the app!
そこでは、現実で苦しむ人の魂が怪物化してしまう現象、『ユメオチ』が起こっていた。
There, a phenomenon called 'Dream Drop' was occurring, where suffering souls turn into monsters.
怪物『コラプサー』を倒して、
We have to defeat the monsters, 'Collapsers,'
みんなの魂を取り戻さないと。
and take back everyone's souls.
そして、魔法少女に変身して、戦うことになった。
And so, we transformed into magical girls and ended up fighting.
みんなの心を助けて、
Saving everyone's hearts,
夢を応援する！
we support their dreams!
それが、魔法少女ホロウィッチ！
That is, Magical Girl HoloWitch!
今日はスペシャルハロウィンステージ。
Today is the special Halloween stage.
ホロキャスの人気配信者が多数出演。
Many popular HoloCas streamers are appearing.
さらに、今ときめく超人気歌手のカノンさんも参加する、
Furthermore, the super popular singer Kanon-san is participating,
超々豪華イベント。
making it a super, super lavish event.
で、その超豪華イベントのオープニングアクトをウチら６人が担当することになって。
And, us six ended up being in charge of the opening act for that super lavish event.
せっかくだし、みんなでホロウィッチの衣装を着て、
Since we're at it, I thought we'd all wear our HoloWitch costumes,
ドカンと派手に盛り上げちゃおうかな、って。
and get things super hype with a bang.
でもいいのかな？
But is that okay?
魔法とか、妖精とか、一応内緒なんだけど…
Magic, fairies, and such are technically a secret...
今日はハロウィンだから！
Today is Halloween!
仮装ってことにすれば、なんとかなるなら！
If we just say it's cosplay, it'll work out somehow!
そう…さ。
Ye... ah.
そろそろ準備したほうがよくない？
Shouldn't we get ready soon?
そうだね。
You're right.
じゃあ、気合い入れていきますか！
Alright, let's get fired up and go!
トリック・オア・トリート！
Trick or Treat!
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅー 足りないでしょ
Obsessed, obsessed, obsessed, it's not enough, right?
こっちおいで 遊ぼうよ
Come over here, let's play!
ねっ・ちゅ・ちゅ・シンドローム
Nekkchu-chu Syndrome
イライラして (Hai!)
Frustrated (Hai!)
イライラ (Hai!)
して (Hai!)
Do it (Hai!)
楽しくいられるために全力
I give my all to keep having fun
イライラ (Hai!)
Frustrated (Hai!)
して (Hai!)
Do it (Hai!)
から (Hai!)
Because (Hai!)
魂抜けるもったいない
If your soul slips away, what a waste!
どうしたら喜んでくれるかな ばーか
How can I make you happy, dummy?
思いついては即行動
As soon as I think of it, I act immediately.
スマイルハンター
Smile Hunter.
こっそり君のツボ
Secretly, your sweet spot,
ピンポイント撃ち抜いちゃう
I'll shoot right through it, pinpoint style.
成功魔法だもん
It's successful magic, after all.
愛の呪文フルキャスト
Full cast of love spells.
コンサートまだまだ仕掛けちゃえ
Let's set up more for the concert!
あっという間に捕まえた
Caught you in the blink of an eye.
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅー シンドローム
Netchu Netchu Netchu Syndrome
いたずらからのハピネス
Happiness from mischief.
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅー したらキュンて
If I get obsessed, obsessed, obsessed, my heart throbs.
錯覚してスマイル
Fall for the illusion and smile.
年中無休カーニバル
Year-round carnival.
好きが重なれば
If our likes overlap,
年中無休カーニバル
Year-round carnival.
お祭り
Festival!
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅー 足りない
Obsessed, obsessed, obsessed, not enough!
こっちおいで
Come here,
遊ぼうよ
let's play!
虜にしちゃう
I'll make you my prisoner.
ほらね
See?
ちょっと待って！ 私の出番は？
Wait a sec! Is it my turn?
つまりどういうこと？？？
So what does that mean???
ピーキーだって集まればつまり最強じゃん？
Even if we're quirky, if we gather, aren't we the strongest?
始まりは違っても
Even if our beginnings were different,
同じ道ゆく
we walk the same path.
ピーキーだって集まればつまり最強じゃん？
Even if we're quirky, if we gather, aren't we the strongest?
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅー シンドローム
Netchu Netchu Netchu Syndrome
高鳴りすぎて発熱
My heart beats too fast, I'm getting a fever.
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅー しとこ
Let's get obsessed, obsessed, obsessed.
とっておきのウィンク
My special wink,
はい！
Yes!
異世界から見せたい
I want to show you from another world,
両手いっぱいの愛
love filling both hands.
こんなに近くにいるよ
I'm this close to you!
ねっちゅー無休で笑いたい
I want to laugh obsessed 24/7.
君と笑い合いたいな
I want to laugh together with you.
余裕ぶっこいていたら
If I act all composed,
いつのまにかすくわれちゃう
I'll be swept off my feet before I know it.
幸せすぎて困っちゃう
I'm so happy it's troubling.
捕まえたら離さない
Once I catch you, I won't let go.
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅー シンドローム
Netchu Netchu Netchu Syndrome
いたずらからのハピネス
Happiness from mischief.
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅー したらキュンて
If I get obsessed, obsessed, obsessed, my heart throbs.
錯覚してスマイル
Fall for the illusion and smile.
年中無休カーニバル
Year-round carnival.
好きが重なれば
If our likes overlap,
年中無休カーニバル
Year-round carnival.
お祭り
Festival!
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅー 足りない
Obsessed, obsessed, obsessed, not enough!
こっちおいで
Come here,
遊ぼうよ
let's play!
虜にしちゃう
I'll make you my prisoner.
ほらね
See?
トリック・オア・トリート！
Trick or treat!
みんな、盛り上がってる？
Everyone, are you getting hyped?
ホロウィッチのオープニングアクト、
How was the HoloWitches'...
どうだった？
...opening act?
ここからもっともっと
From here on out, we're gonna...
盛り上げてくから！
...hype it up even more!
みんなで一緒に楽しもうね！
Let's all have fun together!
今日は我々、ホロウィッチの配信者だけじゃなく
Today, it's not just us HoloWitches streamers,
あの超人気歌手、カノンさんがゲストで来てくださってます！
the super popular singer, Kanon-san, is here as a guest!
カノンさん、どうぞ！
Kanon-san, come on out!
トリック・オア・トリート。
Trick or treat.
みんな。
Everyone.
今日は最後まで、
Let's enjoy this...
よろしく。
...until the very end.
いやまさかね、あのカノンさんと同じステージに立てるとは。
I never thought I'd stand on the same stage as that Kanon-san.
いやほんと、憧れですよ！
Yeah, seriously, I admire her so much!
カノンさんの歌を聞くと、すっごくパワーもらえるのら！
Listening to Kanon-san's songs gives me so much power, nora!
そうそう！こんなに近づいちゃっていいんですか？ってくらいね。
Right, right! It's like, is it really okay to be this close?
うん、めっちゃ元気出るよね。
Yeah, it really cheers you up.
ん？
Hm?
あ、ありがとう！なんでもないから。
Ah, thanks! It's nothing.
次の曲は、みんなも一緒に歌ってほしいの。
For the next song, I want everyone to sing along too.
君たち！遠慮しないで声出してね！
You guys! Don't hold back, let me hear your voices!
声！
Voices!
じょいふる
Joyful
キミの声を 聞かせて
Let me hear your voice
さあ冒険を してみたい
Come on, I want to go on an adventure
楽しむこと はじめよう
Let's start having fun
遊びたい ぜったい (と・たい・たい・たい)
I want to play, definitely (To-tai-tai-tai)
I wanna joy と joy と joy pop な baby
I wanna joy to joy to joy, pop na baby
Joy と joy と joy happy な people
Joy to joy to joy, happy na people
弱虫なんかじゃない
I'm not a coward or anything
自信ありげに peace sign
Confidence with a peace sign
キミの瞳に kiss して
Kissing your eyes
笑いたい ぜったい (と・たい・たい・たい)
I want to laugh, definitely (To-tai-tai-tai)
I wanna joy と joy と joy you-ki な baby
I wanna joy to joy to joy, you-ki na baby
Joy と joy と joy happy な say yeah!
Joy to joy to joy, happy na say yeah!
キミの心はそうもっと (ギュッギュ)
Your heart is, yeah, more (Gyu-gyu)
ボクの心もそういっそ (グッグ)
My heart too, yeah, might as well (Gu-gu)
はじけてるんじゃない It's joyful
Isn't it bursting open? It's joyful
ポピプペポパプ (Yeah!)
Popipupepopapu (Yeah!)
Joy と joy と joy pop な baby
Joy to joy to joy, pop na baby
Joy と joy と joy happy な people
Joy to joy to joy, happy na people
ドジドジしちゃうの なんでだろ
Why do I keep messing up?
ズキズキしちゃうの なんでだろ
Why does it keep throbbing?
華やかに染まるのは
Being dyed so brilliantly
そんな運命なんだ ズキュンとしたいな
That's just fate, I wanna be struck by love
Joyful だけ終わっちゃう
Ending with just joyful
Everybody いつもはちゃう
Everybody, usually it's different
いついつまでも この時を
This moment, forever and ever
最終形はきっと 修正なしで
The final form will surely need no corrections
ウィ・ドゥ・ウィ・ドゥ・ウィ・ドゥ・ドゥ
We do we do we do do
テンポ アップして (と・たい・たい・たい)
Tempo up (To-tai-tai-tai)
I wanna joy と joy と joy you-ki な baby
I wanna joy to joy to joy, you-ki na baby
Joy と joy と joy happy な say yeah!
Joy to joy to joy, happy na say yeah!
キミの心はそうもっと (ギュッギュ)
Your heart is, yeah, more (Gyu-gyu)
ボクの心もそういっそ (グッグ)
My heart too, yeah, might as well (Gu-gu)
はじけてるんじゃない It's joyful
Isn't it bursting open? It's joyful
Joyful ポピプペポパプ
Joyful popipu pepo papu
Joy!
みんな、一緒に歌ってくれてありがとう！
Thanks for singing along with us everyone!
いや～よかったね！
Man, that was great!
会場がね、一体になったって感じでね！
Felt like the whole venue became one!
うん！よかったよかった。
Yeah! It was great, great.
テンション上がるわ、これ！
This really gets me hyped!
さ、さあ次は！
Now, next up!
いよいよカノンさんに歌っていただきます！
We'll finally have Kanon-san sing for us!
君... 大丈夫？
You... are you okay?
え？何？どうしたの？
Eh? What? What's wrong?
え？ええ？
Eh? Eeh?
あわ... あわ... って...
Bub... bub... b-bubbles...
まさか...
Don't tell me...
コラプサー...
Collapsers...
やっぱり...
I knew it...
むぐっ！
Mugu!
取れないんだけど！
I can't get it off!
何これ！？
What is this?!
ちょちょちょちょ！
Wait wait wait wait!
何何？どういうこと？
What what? What does this mean?
コラプサーだ。
It's a Collapser.
ですよねー、どう考えてもねー！
Right? No matter how you look at it!
コラプサー。
A Collapser.
やっぱり！
I knew it!
むーー！
Muuu!
外れ... ない！
It won't... come off!
痛い痛い痛い！
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
割る？
Break it?
怖い怖い怖い！
Scary scary scary!
え、えーと... こういう時は...
U-Um... at times like this...
ト、トリック・オア・トリート！
T-Trick or Treat!
何もかも違うだろ。
Everything about that is wrong.
ぐはっ！
Guh!
ぬおおお！
Nuooo!
顔がね！前後逆になってるよ！
Your face! It's backwards!
出てる出てる！
It's coming out! It's out!
魂のモツが出てる！
Your soul's giblets are coming out!
よいしょ！
Heave-ho!
むぐっ...！
Mugu...!
ま、まあ... コラプサーが出てくるってことは...
W-Well... if Collapsers are appearing...
夢オチしてる人がいるんだ。多分。
Someone must have 'dream-fallen'. Probably.
ミオ先輩？
Mio-senpai?
ミオちゃん？
Mio-chan?
ごめん...
Sorry...
うち... うち... 本当は...
I... I... actually...
ハロウィンのカボチャが... 怖くてだめなの！
I'm scared of Halloween pumpkins... I can't handle them!
え？
Eh?
ちっちゃい頃、パパがハロウィンで...
When I was little, Papa...
あれ被って帰ってきて...
...came home wearing that for Halloween...
ただいまー
I'm home-
うち、パパがカボチャに食べられちゃったんだって思っちゃって...
I thought Papa had been eaten by the pumpkin...
それから...
Since then...
どうしても...
No matter what...
ハロウィンのカボチャだけは...
Halloween pumpkins are the one thing...
無理なの！
...I just can't handle!
うわあああん！
Waaaaah!
いやあああ！
Nooooo!
チェンジ！
Change!
ガーディアンアーム！ミカエル！
Guardian Arm! Michael!
カグラスズ！
Kagura Bell!
ロッタ！キャンディパラソル！
Lotta! Candy Parasol!
ガンバリナ！
Gunbarina!
スノーフレークセイバー！
Snowflake Saber!
フブキマル！
Fubukimaru!
ここは任せて、ミオ！
Leave this to us, Mio!
みんな...
Everyone...
魔法... みんなに見せちゃうけど、いいよね？
I'll show everyone my magic... is that okay?
うん！そんなこと言ってらんないし！
Yeah! We don't have time to worry about that!
だよね。夢オチした人を助ける。それが...
Exactly. Saving those who have dream-fallen. That is...
魔法少女ホロウィッチ！
Magical Girl HoloWitch!
この手を差し伸べ、掴んで、握る！
Reach out this hand, grab, and grip!
天使のホロ、魔法少女カナタ！
Angel Holo, Magical Girl Kanata!
みんなの願いを咲かせる祈り！
A prayer to make everyone's wishes bloom!
巫女のホロ、魔法少女ミコ！
Shrine Maiden Holo, Magical Girl Miko!
甘い幸せ、おすそ分け！
Sharing sweet happiness!
姫のホロ、魔法少女ルーナ！
Princess Holo, Magical Girl Luna!
きらめくお宝、ロックオン！
Lock-on to sparkling treasures!
海賊のホロ、魔法少女マリン！
Pirate Holo, Magical Girl Marine!
心躍らす、トリックスター！
Heart-dancing Trickster!
狐のホロ、魔法少女フブキ！
Fox Holo, Magical Girl Fubuki!
雪のホロ！
Snow Flurry!
魔法少女ラミィ！
Magical Girl Lamy!
ホロウィッチ！
HoloWitch!
フルキャスト！
Full Cast!
いくよー！
Here I go!
ほい！ほい！はーい！
Hoi! Hoi! Haaai!
敵じゃないよ
I'm not an enemy.
仲間だよ
I'm a friend.
コン！
Kon!
やめな！
Stop it!
えい！
Ei!
おいおいおいおい…
Oi oi oi oi...
な、なんかこれ不味くない？
I- Isn't this getting bad?
どんどん強くなってる
They're getting stronger.
みんなが奴らを倒すより
It seems fear and anxiety...
不安と恐れが膨れ上がる方が早いみたい！
...are swelling up faster than we can defeat them!
そんな…
No way...
ウチのせい…
It's my fault...
ウチが… あんなもの
Because I...
怖いって思っちゃうせいで…
...think those things are scary...
そんなこと…
That sort of thing...
分かってるの
I know.
おかしいよね…
It's strange, isn't it...
あんなのが…
That something like that...
こんなどうしようもなく怖いなんて
...could be so hopelessly frightening.
だから…
That's why...
今日も我慢して頑張ろうって
...I thought I'd endure it today and do my best...
思ったのに…
...but...
でも…
But...
でもやっぱり…
But after all...
おかしくなんてないよ
It's not strange at all.
カノンさん？
Kanon-san?
誰にだって苦手なものがある
Everyone has things they are bad at.
怖いもの、嫌いなもの
Scary things. Hated things.
人に何でそんなものがって言われても
Even if people ask 'why are you afraid of that?'...
どうしようもないことってやっぱりあるよ
...there are just some things you can't help.
そうだよ！
That's right!
何が苦手とか！
What you're bad at!
何が怖いかとかは関係なくて！
What you're scared of! None of that matters!
大事なのは…
What's important is...
今、ミオちゃんが辛いって思ってるかどうかだから！
...whether you're feeling pain right now, Mio-chan!
遠慮しないで！
Don't hold back!
頼って欲しいのら！
I want you to rely on us, nora!
だって、そういうのさ…
Because, you know...
ウチらお互い様じゃん！
We're all in this together!
誰かの辛さ…
Someone's pain...
誰かの苦手は他の誰かがカバーする
...someone's weakness will be covered by someone else.
お互いそうやって…
By doing that for each other...
やってきたから今がある！
...we've made it this far!
ひきちぎり！
Hikichigiri!
こんなに頑張れる…
You can work this hard...
ホロウィッチ コラプスは…
The HoloWitch Collapse...
夢オチした人の恐れと不安から生まれる
...is born from the fear and anxiety of those who have fallen into the dream.
その心を深く沈ませて…
Sinking their hearts deep...
夢オチって… どうしてそれを…
Dream-fall...? How do you know that...
でも私は知ってる
But... I know.
君たちなら…
If it's you guys...
ホロウィッチなら…
...If it's HoloWitch...
辛い… 苦しい… 悲しい… キツイ…
It hurts... It's agonizing... It's sad... It's tough...
そんな自分一人の力じゃ抜け出せない暗闇の中に居ても
Even if you are in a darkness you cannot escape alone...
夢を…
Dreams...
光を届けてくれる
...and light will be delivered.
任せて！
Leave it to us!
さあ みんな ホロウィッチが戦ってくれる
Now everyone, HoloWitch will fight for you.
では、私たちに出来るのは？
Then, what can we do?
そう…
Yes...
私たちの声で… 思いで…
With our voices... with our feelings...
彼女たちを応援することだ！
...it is to cheer them on!
いいさ…
Fine then...
Trick or Treat!
あれよと言う間に飲み込まれ
Swallowed up in the blink of an eye
橙色のTidal Wave
An orange Tidal Wave
Jack-o' Jack-o'
HandmadeからOrder-madeまで仕掛ける大流行
From Handmade to Order-made, a massive trend we set up
Hau!
本物から偽物までまとめて大集合
From real to fake, everyone gather 'round
Hau!
So, Lame? それとも？ 不揃いな背丈にお揃いの容姿で？
So, Lame? Or what? Mismatched heights with matching looks?
辟易なクレイも…
Even fed-up clay...
量子も奴隷よ どうしよう奴隷…
Even quantum is a slave, what to do slave...
常識？ 方式？ 放置少女？ Happy Treat?
Common sense? Formula? Neglected girl? Happy Treat?
Trick or Treat から…
From Trick or Treat...
恐ろしなそぞろ
A terrifying restlessness...
浮かり上がり回り月に針が落ちるわ
Floating up and spinning, the needle drops on the moon.
大きな口で笑うカボチャ達が歌うわ
The pumpkins laughing with big mouths will sing.
それが合図 魔物達が目覚め踊るわ
That's the signal, the monsters will awaken and dance.
こうなればあとは思いのまま
Now that it's come to this, it's all as we please.
Hollow! 骨抜きDancer-bo
Hollow! Enthralling Dancer-bo!
Scarecrowも飛び跳ね回る
Even the Scarecrow jumps around.
Hollow! 奇用のTurntable
Hollow! A bizarre Turntable.
クルクルと押し黙り
Spinning round and falling silent...
We gotta party night!
Anyway join the party night!
Woe Woe 不気味なPumpkin
Woe Woe, eerie Pumpkin.
ジャック・オ・ランタン 空気読む無理
Jack-o'-lantern, can't read the room.
まずは素敵なNight
First, a wonderful Night.
振り切れる鼓動
The heartbeat goes off the charts.
我は街のDracula
I am the town's Dracula.
お酒をあおるわ
Downing the sake.
寡黙そうなDullahanも
Even the seemingly quiet Dullahan...
頭を振るわ
...is headbanging.
紳士的なMummyすらも服がはだけるわ
Even the gentlemanly Mummy is bursting out of his clothes.
どうあれど愉快全開のまんま
No matter what, it's full throttle joy.
本性あわらに暴れよう
Reveal your true nature and rampage.
その仮装も正装になる
Even that disguise becomes formal wear.
狂騒曲のTurntable
The Turntable of the Rhapsody.
Ai ai ai! 押し黙り We gotta party night!
Ai ai ai! Fall silent, we gotta party night!
High five! All night! All night!
眠れやしない
I can't sleep.
U la la la la la
Fly high! All night! All night!
鳴り止まない
It won't stop ringing.
古代妄想遊び
Ancient delusion play.
ランタンはまるで魂
The lantern is like a soul.
異世界怪なジャンボリー
A strange other-worldly jamboree.
何喰わぬ Halloween
An innocent Halloween.
Hollow! 骨抜きDancer-bo
Hollow! Enthralling Dancer-bo!
Anyway join the party night!
Kurukuru oshidamari We gotta party night!
Spinning round and silent, we gotta party night!
コルクサの力が乱れてる...
The power of the Corruptors is being disturbed...
恐れと不安が溶けていくんだ
Fear and anxiety are melting away.
歌の力...
The power of song...
みんなの声の力で！
And the power of everyone's voices!
みんな乗ってるね！
Everyone's getting into it!
おかげでこっちもやる気いっぱいなのだ！
Thanks to that, we're full of motivation too!
さあ、行って！ホロウィッチ！
Now, go! HoloWitch!
心を苛むトリックに...
To the trick that torments hearts...
とびっきりのトリートを！
...give them a special treat!
とびっきりのTrickster！
A special Trickster!
みんな応援ありがとう！
Thank you everyone for the support!
思う存分、楽しんじゃうよ！
I'm going to enjoy this to the fullest!
Tricky... Fix!
わぁ！やられた...
Waa! You got me...
なんてね！
Just kidding!
コンコン！
Kon-kon!
ヤーー！
Yaaa!
Innocent Revival!
うん！信じるからね！
Yeah! I believe in you!
みんなの愛が力をくれる！
Everyone's love gives me power!
フブキにゃん！
Fubuki-nyan!
ラミィちゃんナイス！
Lamy-chan, nice!
それじゃ...決めちゃうよ！
Alright then... let's finish this!
Unidears Lamination!
Thrashing Snow Compressor!
Yeah!
みこみこ先輩！
Miko-Miko Senpai!
サンキュー、ルーナたん！
Thank you, Lunatan!
セイクリッド・スフィア！
Sacred Sphere!
みんな、みこのエリートなとこ...
Everyone, Miko's elite side...
そんなに見たいんだ！
You want to see it that much!
しょうがないね！
Can't be helped then!
てい！
Tei!
みんなと一緒に...
Together with everyone...
どんなマジやるなのら！
Whatever magic we do, nanora!
サイバー・スクランブル・セイバー！
Cyber Scramble Saber!
プリンセス・フェイバー！
Princess Favor!
スラッシュ・ヘイロー！
Slash Halo!
サンキューかなた！
Thank you, Kanata!
みんなの想い、全部乗っけて...
Carrying everyone's feelings...
飛び込むしかねぇだろ！
I gotta dive in!
君たち、ちょうど欲しいとこに来てくれるじゃん。
You guys show up exactly where I want you.
みんな揃って...いい的だからね！
Gathered all together... you make good targets!
よっしゃあ！
Alright!
セレスティアル・リンギング・オーバー・スプラッシュ・ベル！
Celestial Ringing Over Splash Bell!
あいつらでラストだ。
That's the last of them.
決めだよ！みんな！
Finish it! Everyone!
チェンジ！ホロウィッチステッキ！
Change! HoloWitch Stick!
ウィッチブルーム！
Witch Broom!
フルキャスト！
Full Cast!
ミオ先輩、もう大丈夫そ？
Mio-senpai, seems like it's okay now?
あ、うん。
Ah, yeah.
その...見ないようにすればなんとか。
Well... if I try not to look, I can manage somehow.
わかるよ。
I get it.
白上も高いとこいくと下見れないからね。
Shirakami can't look down when she goes to high places either.
ミオ先輩なのら。
Mio-senpai, nanora.
蟲はなるべく見ないようにしてるなのら。
I try not to look at bugs as much as possible, nanora.
ありがとう、みんな。
Thank you, everyone.
みんなが助けてくれたみたいに...
Just like everyone helped me...
うちも、みんなが辛い時、苦しい時があったら...
I also, if everyone has painful or difficult times...
絶対、絶対力になるから。
I'll definitely, definitely be your strength.
さて、これでめでたしめでたし。
Well then, and they all lived happily ever after.
でもいいんだけど…
Or so it could be, but...
みんな！
Everyone!
ホロウィッチの活躍、もっと見たいんじゃない？
Don't you want to see more of the HoloWitches in action?
見たい！
We want to see!
だそうだけど。
That's what they say.
え？こっち？こっち振るの？
Eh? Us? You're passing this to us?
え、あ、いや… やります！
Eh, ah, n-no... We'll do it!
よし！やるよ、みんな！
Alright! Let's do this, everyone!
おー！
Yeah!
空は青く澄み渡り 海を目指して歩く
The sky is clear and blue, as we walk towards the sea.
怖いものなんてない
There is nothing to fear.
僕らはもう一人じゃない
We are not alone anymore.
大切な何かが 壊れたあの夜に
On that night when something precious broke,
僕は星を探して 一人で歩いていた
I was walking alone, searching for the stars.
ペルセウス座流星群
The Perseids meteor shower...
君も見てただろうか
...were you watching it too?
僕は元気でやってるよ
I'm doing well over here.
君は今どこにいるの？
Where are you right now?
「方法」という悪魔に とり憑かれないで
Don't let the devil called "Method" possess you.
「目的」という大事なものを
The important thing called "Purpose"...
思い出して
...please remember it.
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue,
海を目指して歩く
As we walk towards the sea.
怖いものなんてない
There is nothing to fear.
僕らはもう一人じゃない
We are not alone anymore.
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue,
海を目指して歩く
As we walk towards the sea.
怖くても大丈夫
It's okay even if you're scared.
僕らはもう一人じゃない
We are not alone anymore.
大切な何かが 壊れたあの夜に
On that night when something precious broke,
僕は君を探して
I was searching for you,
一人で歩いていた
Walking all on my own.
あの日から僕らは
Ever since that day,
一人で海を目指す
Each of us aimed for the sea alone.
「約束のあの場所」で
At "that promised place",
必ずまた会おうと
Vowing that we would surely meet again.
「世間」という悪魔に
By the devil called "Society",
惑わされないで
Don't be led astray.
自分だけが決めた答えを
The answer that only you decided...
思い出して
...please remember it.
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue,
海を目指して歩く
As we walk towards the sea.
怖いものなんてない
There is nothing to fear.
僕らはもう一人じゃない
We are not alone anymore.
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue,
海を目指して歩く
As we walk towards the sea.
怖くても大丈夫
It's okay even if you're scared.
僕らはもう一人じゃない
We are not alone anymore.
煌めきのような命の中で
In this life that flashes like a sparkle,
君に出会えて
To have been able to meet you...
僕は本当に良かった
...I am truly glad.
街を抜け海に出たら
Once we leave the town and reach the sea,
次はどこを目指そうか
Where shall we aim for next?
僕らはまた出かけよう
Let's set out on a journey again,
愛しいこの世界を
Into this beloved world.
みんな、今日はありがとう！
Everyone, thank you for today!
最高に楽しいハロウィンだったよね？みんな！
It was the most fun Halloween, wasn't it? Everyone!
ちょっとアクシデントもあったけどさ
There were a few accidents, but...
そう言うのも含めて
including all of that,
いい思い出になったんじゃない？
didn't it make for a good memory?
だねー！
Totally!
いい思い出…
A good memory...
おい！
Hey!
さて、そろそろお時間となって参りましたが
Well then, it is almost time to wrap up...
アンコール！
Encore!
それじゃあアンコールにお応えして！
Then, in answer to your encore!
この曲、歌っちゃうのら！
We're gonna sing this song, nora!
はじまりの魔法 -charm-！
Hajimari no Mahou -charm-!
君に魔法をかけるよ
I'll cast a magic spell on you,
見返せるおまじない
a charm to prove them all wrong.
始まりを告げる衝動が響く
The impulse signaling the beginning resounds.
気付いた時がいつだってスタートラインなんだ
Whenever you realize it, that is your start line.
何者でもなかった日々を超えたのは
What surpassed the days when I was nobody,
見つけたばかりのちっぽけな輝きの原石
was the tiny unpolished gem of radiance I just found.
どうして私だけ上手くいかないんだろう
Why am I the only one who can't do things well?
自分以外の全てが眩しく見えるけど
Everything other than myself looks so dazzling, but...
ねえ君に見つけて欲しくて
Hey, I wanted you to find me.
なりたい私になる今こそ
I'll become the 'me' I want to be, right now.
そうだ 叶えたい掴みたい夢があるから
That's right, because I have a dream I want to fulfill and seize.
塞ぎ込んだ昨日ごとも連れて行くんだ
I'll take even my depressed yesterdays along with me.
信じる力が奇跡を起こすように
So that the power of believing creates a miracle.
君に魔法をかけるよ
I'll cast a magic spell on you,
見返せるおまじない
a charm to prove them all wrong.
叶わぬ望みと
Unfulfillable hopes,
叶わない願い
and unfulfillable wishes,
それぞれが等しく流れてく世界で
in a world where they all flow equally...
何を求めて歩き続けるんだろう
what are we seeking as we keep walking?
いつでもこの場所で迷うけど
I always get lost in this place, but...
君がくれたこの空が
this sky that you gave me,
見えない翼をくれたね
gave me invisible wings, didn't it?
そうだ 照らしたい届けたい人がいるから
That's right, because there are people I want to shine on and reach.
たとえ一人置いてけぼり食らうと怯えてたんだ
Even if I was frightened of being left behind all alone...
愛したい応えたい自分自身の期待
I want to love, I want to answer my own expectations.
正解なんて超えて行こう 未体験の先へ
Let's go beyond the 'correct answer', to the unexperienced future.
どんな場所でもいいよ
Any place is fine.
どんな姿でもいい
Any form is fine.
追いかけたいんだ あの煌めきを
I want to chase after that sparkle.
希望 野望 光 痛み 力 全て抱きしめて持って行こう
Hope, ambition, light, pain, power; hold them all close and let's go.
ほら 繋げたい広げたい道があるから
Look, because there's a path I want to connect and expand.
ここから始まる物語を一緒に
The story starting from here, together we'll...
ひとりじゃないから
Because you are not alone,
君に魔法をかけるよ
I'll cast a magic spell on you.
We can save all your dream
最高のステージだったよ ホロウィッチ
That was the best stage, holoWitches.
ホントホント！
True, true!
みんな お疲れ様
Good work, everyone.
カノンさん
Kanon-san.
あの 今日は本当にありがとうございました
Um... thank you so much for today.
それで あなたはどうしてユメオチとか僕達のことを…
And, why did you help us with the Dream Drop and everything...
私 前にユメオチして
I suffered from a Dream Drop before,
君たちに助けられたことがあるんだ
and I was saved by you all.
ええ！？
Huh?!
だから あの時の自分と同じように
So, just like myself back then,
ユメオチして苦しんでいる誰かを見ると 放っておけなくて
when I see someone suffering from a Dream Drop, I can't leave them alone.
あと 実は
Also, actually...
今日このステージに出ることにしたのも
the reason I decided to appear on this stage today
君たちが出るって聞いたからなんだ
is because I heard you all would be appearing.
もう一度会えたらって思って
I hoped I could meet you again.
だから今日は… えっと…
So today was... um...
すごく嬉しかった！
I was really happy!
これからも頑張ってね ホロウィッチ
Keep doing your best, holoWitches.
そ それじゃ！
We- Well then!
また！
Again!
ぜひまた！
See you again, definitely!
あの人自身がユメオチして ホロウィッチに助けられていたから
Because that person himself suffered a Dream Drop and was saved by the holoWitches,
知っていたんだ
he knew.
ユメオチした時の辛さも
The pain of suffering a Dream Drop,
そんな時 誰かが手を差し伸べてくれることの嬉しさも
and the joy of having someone reach out a hand in that moment.
そっか
I see.
みこ達が少しでも誰かの力になれたら
If we could be of help to someone even a little...
その誰かが また別の誰かの力になってくれるんだね
then that someone will become strength for someone else again.
そうだね
That's right.
しかもさ そんだけじゃなくて ウチらの力になってくれたりもするわけじゃん
Plus, it's not just that, they also end up giving us strength too.
あの人や 今日応援してくれたみんなみたいに
Like that person, and everyone who cheered for us today.
それって…
That's...
それって！
That's!
それってすっごく…
That's super...
すっごくトリート！
Super Treat!
絶対大丈夫
It's absolutely gonna be okay.
ただ真っ直ぐでいることも
Just being straightforward is also...
楽じゃない日もあるよね
there are days when it's not easy, right?
あきらめも苦しみも 重なっていく心解き放とう
Let's unleash the heart where resignation and suffering pile up.
夢を歌おう魔法に乗せて
Let's sing of dreams, riding on magic.
何度も立ち上がる 君と一緒に進んでく
I'll move forward together with you, who stands up again and again.
夢は
The dream,
夢はまだ終わらない
the dream isn't over yet.
未来を取り戻そう
Let's take back the future.
何度だって笑ってもう一回
Laugh as many times as it takes, one more time.
歩き始めよう
Let's start walking.
holoWitches on your side
夢の先へ
To beyond the dream.
飛び出すんだ 今日
Let's fly out today!
踏ん張っていても
Even if we try our hardest,
うまくいかない日の方が
days where things don't go well
多く感じちゃったりするよね
can feel like they're more common, right?
でも不安も
But don't carry
悲しみも
your anxiety and sadness
抱えないで
all by yourself.
ひとりじゃない
You are not alone.
希望の種は
The seeds of hope...
明日になったら
...when tomorrow comes...
一番に輝く綺麗な花が咲くよ
...will bloom into the most shining, beautiful flowers!
夢を歌を
Carrying dreams and songs
魔法に乗せて
upon magic,
何度も立ち上がる
we'll stand up again and again,
君と一緒に進んでく
and move forward together with you.
夢は夢はまだ終わらない
The dream, the dream isn't over yet!
未来を取り戻そう
Let's take back the future!
何度だって笑って
Laughing again and again,
もう一回
one more time,
歩き始めよう
let's start walking.
Holo Witches On Your Side
夢の先へ
Towards the future of our dream!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
アニメーションMV「微かな夕陽」公式設定資料集 2026年1月30日発売
Animation MV "Kasuka na Yuuhi" Official Setting Materials. On sale Jan 30, 2026!
ウルトラジャンプにて連載中 単行本最新2巻まで発売中
Serialized in Ultra Jump. Volumes 1 & 2 on sale now!